I always knew Ko Geum was a little weird.
5 YEARS AGO, WINTER
Hello. Congratulations.
- Good morning.
- Hello.
Congratulations, Assistant Director Puck.
- Did they call you today?
- No.
But you come every day.
Do you like being here?
You are a fanatic.
I adore I like it very much.
Everyone who knew Ko Gyom thought so too.
I asked not to do this.
But why? Am I not allowed to help?
This is no help.
I don't want to be gossiped about.
So give me peace.
But no one...
I guess you got it.
I thought,
that he will finally give me peace.
But...
ONE OF EACH!
Nothing left?
I am the director here. You didn't leave anything for me?
You said you wouldn't eat anything
because you are too nervous on the court.
You literally screamed.
I didn't… I didn't scream.
Why wasn't it sent?
enough snacks for everyone?
Are we on a tight budget?
Nothing left?
I was late.
Do not chew here.
Sorry.
- Kim Mubi.
- Have you arrived?
Shall we switch places?
What?
Why? What is it, Goem?
We haven't finished our conversation.
I still have a few questions. Well, because
I thought we had arrived.
- What is it?
- What?
Ha?
Sleep-sleep
can i sleep
Can someone help me?
Yes.
Now. I will help!
Mr. Ma ordered it to be postponed.
OK. And this?
- No, let's postpone it first.
- First this.
Maybe I'm the weird one, not Ko Gyeom?
That's about work.
OK. That's all for today.
That's all for today!
- We are finishing!
- Let's roll up!
- All well done.
Great work!
"WEALTH AND PROSPERITY"
REQUISITES
FILMING CANCELED DUE TO SNOW FALL
The snow will have to be shoveled tomorrow.
He was as carefree as always.
Why are you taking so long?
Everyone left long ago.
- Were you waiting for me?
- Yes.
Why?
To pick you up
It was not possible?
But now
I begin to look at everything differently.
Why?
I like you.
Is this one of your lines?
You know that I have no words.
I thought that its simplicity -
this is proof of his sincerity.
I like you.
Is it forbidden?
Maybe that's why I fell for him.
Mubi.
But...
I…
I want you to like me again.
…that's wrong.
Don't talk nonsense.
It would be foolish to do it twice.
Kim Mubi!
I will never do such a pathetic thing again.
EPISODE 5
NO ONE CAN PREPARE
LOVE AND FEAR YOU
What is it? Are you planning to rob your neighbors?
I need something.
That's why I'm thinking how to get it.
I haven't seen that sparkle in my eyes for a long time.
I'm talking about a girl who lives there.
Like a good girl.
Have you seen Kim Mubi? Did you know about her?
What?
What is the girl you were chasing
a few years ago, - our neighbor?
Even the neighborhood kids know
that you like her
What's stopping you?
It's because of me...
No.
I swear, not because of you, but because of me.
And more importantly, she hates me.
Like many people on the Internet.
I don't care about that.
A star always has
many fans and haters.
However
I don't want Mubi to hate me.
What is it?
"I don't want Mubi to hate me."
are you nine
what's wrong with you
You know nothing! what do you know
You have a problem.
Why does he come out again?
The poor boy wanted to go home
and you didn't let him sleep.
Playing video games is the best way
distract from thoughts.
Where is Jung Hoo? Already gone?
He said he would be back soon.
I could just ignore
words by Ko Gyom.
And instead I lost sleep.
It's like a memory from the past.
Why did you come out again?
And at such a time!
Mubi and I all night...
I thought we got along last time.
What?
I asked not to go to her just like that.
If you don't have friends
I'll hang out with you, I said.
It's not interesting with you. Without insults.
Wait!
You make me sad.
Last time you stayed
I have five hours at home.
It's called having a good time.
We had fun!
You are obsessed with me
because of my baby girl, right?
You are not her type at all.
What?
But what do you know, little potato...
Mubi said that a psycho lives opposite.
Why should I help you?
What? Psycho?
Did Mubi say that?
- Yes.
- About me?
U Jung Hoo, go eat breakfast!
Where is he?
- Jeong Hoo, go eat!
- Good.
- At Jung Hoo!
- What, Mubi?
- Go already.
- I'm going
Goem, you're not her type.
Oh you...
- What were you doing there?
- A slipper.
There was a very ugly cat.
"MELODY"
SCREENWRITER: SONG CHU A
DIRECTOR: KIM MUBY
Why does she keep coming here?
So annoying.
I don't know what you said at first
but the last words were
"so annoying," director Kim.
Do you read lips?
Impressive.
I don't want to be here either
but I am on important business.
What is it?
He agreed to write the music.
Let me remind you. I have to listen first.
Okay, I understand. But you will like it.
It's like you parted ways badly.
Are you sure about this?
It will be necessary constantly
communicate at work,
and you will end up fighting.
I apologize, of course, but we are all adults.
Argue with a colleague -
it's kind of childish.
Let's see.
What is it?
Looking for a place to shoot?
Prompt?
aren't you going
When I think we've got it together
you're acting like we're strangers again.
bye
Come on.
Greetings! Goem, come here!
You saw each other last time.
I didn't have a chance to say hello properly.
Nice to meet you.
It must have been difficult for you.
- Do you want a drink?
- Yes, of course.
he's not like that
but you know how people are.
He got it because of a simple misunderstanding.
Yes, I saw director Ku's interview.
What an untimely coincidence.
You probably thought it was unfair.
Not entirely unfair.
The review was too harsh.
I didn't think it was unfair.
Pour you?
Thank you.
And now let's drink. Cheers!
Printed text has limitations.
It does not convey facial expressions
and the tone of the author's voice,
so I realized I could give up
more hostile than one would like.
Perhaps that is why my articles are not perfect.
If I were to review your movie
live in front of you, with a smile on your face,
you probably wouldn't be so offended.
That's why I'm asking
your understanding
And what did I say?
He seems rude
but he is a decent guy.
Let's drink and forget about all resentments.
He got it anyway.
- Let's be!
wait Allow me.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
Thank you. I am in your debt again.
Please.
But to him!
You cannot occupy the entire lane.
Don't you see how narrow it is?
Sorry.
Motorcycle beat! You will pay me!
Sir! I saw everything.
What do you say to a person who has just been beaten up?
What? Did I knock him down?
He himself flew at me!
I saw
how that thing hit that man in the arm.
Apologize to him!
Why should I?
you either apologize
or appear in court
and compensate him for the damage.
Sorry.
I was just distracted.
And this, in your opinion, is sincere?
I am sincerely sorry.
I didn't realize I had touched you.
Nothing. Everything is fine.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Are you OK?
Yes.
You are always so kind.
I
your mother is also kind.
my mother
It doesn't look like her.
Well, not friendly,
but even though she has a gloomy look...
You are very similar.
And you don't look like your brother at all.
You seem so attentive and he…
Too indifferent?
Probably not bad
talk about him in front of his brother
but he really is too indifferent.
That's why it's attractive.
There is nothing attractive about that guy.
Does your brother always take everything as a joke?
He seems too carefree.
But sometimes...
when you carry a heavy burden…
you try to make it easy
because you can't handle it.
I wish he was carefree.
But he is not like that, and that worries me a lot.
Chun Tae.
Of course. Good.
Why are you doing this?
Because...
i love cinema
And somehow it turned out that way.
Like everyone else in the industry.
We all love movies.
Yes, cinema is fascinating.
Apparently.
but you know
enough of me
What?
I'm crazy about movies like everyone else
but i feel like i'm gonna hate him
if i continue
After reading your review
and looking around,
I realized that I lack talent.
At first I didn't care.
But lately I feel
strength to throw everything.
It's not because of what you wrote
so don't worry.
I just want to leave everything…
while I still like the movie.
I'm drunk as a chip.
You should not do this.
Mubi
No. Koh Gome.
Go Goem!
Yes, you must.
Only once.
The subscriber is temporarily unavailable.
Try later...
Haven't unblocked my number yet.
It's cruel.
did you wake up
Yes.
- Hold on.
- Thank you.
When did I get back yesterday?
How did I get home?
You came at two in the morning.
And quite interesting.
"Quite interesting"? That is?
What is it?
It belongs to our neighbor.
- Did I see Mubi yesterday?
- You saw Mubi.
What? As?
No, don't say!
No! say What happened?
No, don't say.
No!
tell me In detail.
You went out late yesterday,
so I woke up and looked out the window.
Please open it. Open it!
Near the neighbors' house
flailed his arms and legs...
Open the door, Mubi!
…boy, similar
on an aerial dancer.
Mubi.
That's why I left immediately.
- And it was you.
- Unblock my number.
However
someone got ahead of me.
Kim Mubi.
Shut up and go away.
Unblock my number.
- Unlock.
- Let go. Let me go!
Unblock my number please.
Unlock while you're here!
Then I picked you up and brought you home.
To be more precise, attracted like a dog.
Chune! I had to be picked up immediately
and not to watch that circus!
You talk a lot of nonsense all the time.
I didn't know you were so drunk.
God, what should I do now?
Who knows
I told her yesterday that you are very sensible.
I will look bad.
It must be her.
Devil!
Give it back
Once again you will get drunk and make a scene -
I'll call the police right away.
Understood
how are you
If you think
she could report me to the police
but did not declare.
Maybe it means
that she doesn't hate me?
You're still drunk.
maybe
I still have a chance.
Gomme.
It's good to be an optimist, but...
First, I need a plan.
I will find Jung Hoo and ask.
He should sober up.
Does he remember or not?
Mubi.
Do you remember Chun San?
This is your father's friend.
Yes, I remember. And what?
He just called.
He said he wanted to
to ask you for a favor.
What does he want from me?
What? Where did he go?
Who this time?
They come and go as they please.
Greetings.
Are you from the store?
what are you doing
Who let you break in here?
Hi Honsi.
I invited her.
What?
I said I would work with you.
But you are crossing the line.
What are the limits? I am here to discuss matters.
Think you can come whenever you want?
- Did you change the number?
- What?
Or you blocked me.
I would warn you
if I could contact you.
Did you block her?
It hurts a lot.
You can't just block...
shut up
Well? What is it? why are you here
we will work together
and we will have to see each other often.
You said you wanted my music.
I will work alone
so let's stay away from each other.
It won't work.
If you read the script,
then you should know that music -
this is the story and the main character.
Therefore, we need to discuss everything.
I read the script.
The music must be unsurpassed.
That's right.
To write such music,
we need to share inspiration
so I will come more often.
"Inspiration"?
"Share"?
I can handle it myself.
Understand me correctly, Xi Chun.
The job is not yours yet.
The director has yet to decide
that music is worth something.
So I have to listen to her.
"Worth something"?
You two need to calm down.
I thought she would just hire
an inexperienced author?
Don't say that. He has experience.
It was you who begged me to work with you.
And you agreed to it, so let's work.
You said you were putting everything on the line.
She is right.
You agreed, so try.
Song Choo A.
Is it because of pride? Are you still not reconciled?
Don't talk like that.
You better go.
I must have lost my mind.
I will not be able to work with you.
No, I'm not going anywhere.
I spoke clearly.
I want to make a movie
and met a worthy director.
I need your music.
I'm not going to back down.
Okay, fight.
You never grew up.
And who is this director?
You think so. It doesn't concern me.
I won't do that.
- You will do it!
What is the problem?
You have to do it.
You can't turn your nose.
Honsi, come to your senses.
How much longer will you be idle?
Are you telling me to put up with this shit?
Chu Ah, you were too sharp, agree.
- Do you regret what you said?
- Don't climb.
This is a great opportunity for both of you.
Why spoil everything?
If you are an adult, act accordingly.
get up
Shake hands.
Virtual handshake. Now everything is fine.
Let's think about what's next.
Do not climb!
This is our business.
ok
not sure now is the right time
but I'll say it while we're all here together.
I fell in love with someone again.
Thank you for your support. I will do my best.
Invertebrate beetle.
Did he leave his studio?
Obviously, because of me.
That we acted like everything was fine
probably made him angrier.
I want to apologize.
I didn't know what you went through.
It must have been very difficult for you
and I was not around.
I'm sorry I'm serious.
No need to apologize.
I'm fine.
To be honest, it wasn't that difficult.
You better…
tell me about kim mubi.
DIRECTOR: KIM MUBY
It was so childish.
And none of them followed me.
Did Golem convince you of this?
And you will give Kim Mubi for this?
I will not give it away.
I will help him just once.
That's all I have to offer.
Cassette.
I didn't watch it when I was little.
Why? Didn't you watch it with your friends?
I had no friends.
None of the boys wanted to play with me.
I had a tube sticking out of it,
and I was very weak.
Is everything good now?
I recovered from a difficult operation.
Am I not healthy?
It hurt so much that I thought:
"It is better to die than to live like this."
But it's good that I persevered.
Only Mubi was friends with me.
I played with her every day
so i watched instead
"Sailor Moon" and "Wedding Peach".
Consider it an honor that I let you
spend a movie day with us.
You should thank me profusely.
In fact, you have a good opportunity.
Just about to tell you or not?
- What is it?
- And what? What is it?
Wait! Gomm!
OK! I will tell!
Good.
We need to arrange a meeting for you.
Yes.
Do I have to tell you?
Tell me while I'm good.
Clear.
Boss
God
That's what your dad always did.
He recently found out that you are a director
and asked very carefully.
If you don't want to, refuse.
Mubi's father was a big movie buff.
He must have rewatched all the movies.
Every year at this time, our community
arranged a movie screening in the open air.
Her dad did the training.
He chose the films himself.
It was cool.
This year too?
I saw the announcement on the pole.
28TH SUMMER FILM SHOWING IN DORA FOREST
Take her there?
28TH ANNUAL FILM SHOWING IN DORA FOREST
It was my dad's favorite time of year.
He especially liked to choose films.
What will we show this time?
What do you say?
Here is a good one.
Why hasn't anyone heard of this movie?
He liked to look for films by directors,
which were overlooked.
- Are you not hot?
- No.
Congratulations.
I heard you wanted to show my movie
so I decided to stop by.
Directed by Koo Yeon-sik?
- Yes.
- He is probably a director.
- Thank you for coming.
- Yes.
It's a small event, but people like it.
- Thank you once again.
- Please.
- Nice.
- Yes.
How can I…
Thank you, Mubi.
Please.
You probably didn't lack for work.
It's a pity that your father is gone
to show your film myself.
You know how he loved and was proud of it.
Either way, it's nice to do it again
after so many years.
We will take care of everything else.
Find yourself a good place
and enjoy watching.
OK.
This can be left in the tent.
- There?
- Yes.
why are you here
I am an employee.
Don't pull...
Do not pull too hard.
Your side is too low.
No, yours is too high.
What?
Seriously, miss.
We need to raise it higher so that people can see.
Don't be a smartass.
13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19...
My God!
What happened? Oh…
I'm sorry
I didn't see you because of this thing.
No, thank you.
Come on.
What were you doing anyway?
Did you measure something?
One mat? Please.
28TH ANNUAL FILM SHOW
Chune what are you doing I had to call.
I will manage.
What is it?
Nothing special.
Magical atmosphere.
You brought so much.
Friends!
"Friends"? Since when are you friends with them?
They even brought lanterns.
That's good.
Let's go and sit with them.
It will be dark without lights.
What? who said
What? I say
Come on. I will take
Come on. after you
Please.
Did you cook it yourself?
You are so young and cook so well.
Learned
Looks delicious.
- Chun, may I?
- Of course.
Thanks for the food!
Mom, have you seen this movie before?
We were here together a long time ago.
Are these fried patties? Yubuchobap.
- Take your time, taste it.
- Yes, ma'am.
What should I eat first?
Deliciously?
One dry martini.
We are closed, ma'am.
It's not time yet.
We are closed, so leave.
Sir are you closed?
- Huh?
- What?
- Closed?
No.
We are not closing, take your time.
Your bartender told me to leave.
You give me a headache.
Stop it. I have to…
I only asked you to leave. Clear?
Ask out loud why should I leave?
Thank you.
Have you written anything yet?
- I...
- Don't you dare say that you changed your mind.
You didn't agree to
to quit now
I understand that I get on your nerves
but work is work.
So bear with me, it's hard for me too.
And why is it difficult for you?
I don't know. Probably because you too.
- Do you know me so well?
- I think so.
Wait until I finish.
Let's go.
- Give it to me.
- Thank you.
Why do you need so many things?
They were in the locker.
It is difficult to carry everything at once.
Leave unnecessary things at school.
Not worth it.
My dad loved so many things.
One day I will show my film here.
And I will never forget,
how he looked at what he loved.
You've already seen this movie.
Why are you watching with such enthusiasm?
Because every time it's a different feeling.
The second and third times are completely different.
Have you watched it that many times?
i love movies
Mubi.
This time I was flirting.
But I was always worried...
Yes?
Yes, I understand.
OK.
…that my father probably didn't like me that much.
Mubi.
Unfortunately, something urgent happened.
I'm sorry, sunshine. I will call
When I thought he would finally be around,
he disappeared again.
Butcher shop.
Yes, order?
I told myself to stop hoping.
VIDE BAR
Honestly, you surprised me.
I thought you left the bar a long time ago.
But you still work hard.
You always said you'd get out of here
and became a real expert
from various cocktails.
are you going to the studio
Just don't say you already wrote the song.
I remember you worked very quickly...
what are you doing
Something wrong?
You said you know me
and why is it difficult for me
What?
You seem to feel the same way.
What are you grinding?
Isn't that what guys want?
from ex-girlfriends?
Crazy goat.
So listen.
Enough testing me. stop it
Why did you do that?
Because I was angry.
do you hate me so much
If you hate it so much, then fine.
I will stop
I need time.
You decided when to break up with me
and when to return.
Maybe...
give me time to digest this.
I got confused.
But I try to accept this strange situation.
sorry I…
I didn't know you felt this way.
I thought…
since so many years have passed, I…
You don't know me well.
I didn't know you well either.
That's why we parted ways.
Where are you?
You cover the screen.
can you sit down I can't see the screen!
I don't see
Shall we turn around?
Shall we go back?
I think I'm drowning myself.
enough playing
like then
I didn't play
when he said i like you
I don't believe you.
I had a premonition, I was hoping for something,
and you played a joke on me.
You know how terrible it is to feel anxiety,
and then be left alone?
- I...
- Was it a confession?
what did you say
You said you had a premonition
and hoped for something.
It sounded like a confession.
Actually, I should be complaining.
You were the first to reach out.
You were the first to kiss me.
I was only the first to confess my feelings.
But why do you object?
Why are you behaving like this? What do you…
are you afraid
I guess I'm coming across as a weirdo again.
I hoped
you will understand my feelings.
To a girl who has survived difficulties...
I wanted to give a gift of lightness.
Ko Geum's carefreeness knows no bounds.
I've had enough.
I like you again.
I still like you, Kim Mubi.
And I wanted to believe him again.
This is pathetic.
If you don't stop...
This time I made the first move.
LIKE IN THE MOVIE
No, I have.
- Is it tasty?
- Yes.
hold on
Please.
dear god
Satisfied?
How nice.
Where is Mubi? It's about to start. Call her.
- She left the phone here.
- What?
hold on
KO GYOM
Translation of subtitles: Natalya Kovalyshyn